{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": "What two things did God create in the beginning? (Genesis 1:3-5)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "The light and the darkness "
        },
        {
          "choice": "The heavens and the earth"
        },
        {
          "choice": "The land and the sea "
        },
        {
          "choice": "The world and the stars "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "The heavens and the earth",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the Spirit of God doing initially before the 7 days of creation began (Gen. 1:2)? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Breathing life on the land "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Sweeping over the earth like a wind "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Speaking to the waters "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Hovering over the waters "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Hovering over the waters ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God create in the first day? (Genesis 1:1)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Water "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Light "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Celestial bodies (planets, moons, stars, etc.)"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Air "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Light ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "On the first day after God made the light, what two things did He separate (Gen. 1:4)? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Land and the sea "
        },
        {
          "choice": "The light on the earth and the light of His presence "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Light and darkness "
        },
        {
          "choice": "The sun and moon "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Light and darkness ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God create on the second day? (Genesis 1:6-8)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Sky &heaven "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Oceans &seas"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Outer space &stars "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Clouds &Vapors"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Sky &heaven ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God create on the third day? (Genesis 1:9-13)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Plant Life "
        },
        {
          "choice": "The seas "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Land "
        },
        {
          "choice": "All of these"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "All of these",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " What did God create on the fourth day? (Genesis 1:14-19)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Animals "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Celestial bodies (planets, moons, stars, etc.)"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Plants "
        },
        {
          "choice": "The waters   "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Celestial bodies (planets, moons, stars, etc.)",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God create on the fifth day? (Genesis 1:20-23)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "All animals "
        },
        {
          "choice": "All animals except those that live on the land"
        },
        {
          "choice": "All animals except those that live in the ocean"
        },
        {
          "choice": "All animals except those that live in the sky "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "All animals except those that live on the land",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " Which did God NOT create on the sixth day? (Genesis 1:24-27) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Some animals   "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Man"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Birds"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Woman"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Birds",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God create on the seventh day?  (Genesis 2:2)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Man"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Language "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Woman"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Nothing "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Nothing ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God think of His work? (Genesis 1:31)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "It was sufficient"
        },
        {
          "choice": "It was good"
        },
        {
          "choice": "It was perfect"
        },
        {
          "choice": "It was glorious"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "It was good",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God call the firmament? (Genesis 1:8)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Earth"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Heaven"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Cloud "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Space "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Heaven",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God call the dry land and the waters? (Genesis 1:20) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Mountains; Oceans"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Valleys; Lakes"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Earth; Seas"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Stone; Water "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Earth; Seas",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did God create humans? (Genesis 1:26-27) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "In His image"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Through evolution of primates"
        },
        {
          "choice": "The goodness and love"
        },
        {
          "choice": "The dust of the earth "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "In His image",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": "God command the following to Adam and Eve except? (Genesis 1:28) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Have dominion over all living things "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Work and be industrious"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Be fruitful and multiply"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Subdue the earth "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Work and be industrious",
      "type": "epi_1"
    }
  ]
}





